Guide to the Richard Strassberg Collection of ILR Buffalo Extension Web Exhibit Files
Strassberg, Richard, Collection of ILR Buffalo Extension Web Exhibit Files
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Richard Strassberg Collection of ILR Buffalo Extension Web Exhibit Files 1897-2003
/4267
Strassberg, Richard
1.2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Richard Strassberg was Associate Director of the Martin P. Catherwood Library and as Director of the Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives. He held the position of the Director of the Archives from 1978-2007 and was appointed Associate Catherwood Director in 1980.
Following internships at the Colorado State Archives in 1966 and the Colorado State Historical Society in 1967, he was hired as Assistant Archivist for Technical Processes in Cornell's Department of Regional History and University Archives in 1968. In 1970, he was appointed the Technical Processes Coordinator for the department. In 1971, Richard joined the staff of the Labor-Management Documentation Center as its Associate Archivist and moved to his present position as Director of the Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives in 1977. (The Center was renamed in 1995.) The Kheel Center is among the leading repositories of its kind in North America.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Strassberg, Richard
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
/4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files
CONTAINER LIST
- Buffalo (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Missing Pages from Illustrated History of the United Trades and Labor Council of Erie County (1897) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Project NELL, 1942-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  1 floppy disc
- Dana Ford (tex1) .txt (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Illustrated History of the United Trades and Labor Council, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- University Microfilms International, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Buffalo Labor History Project- Web Page, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  1 CD; PDF Files
- Buffalo Project, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Illustrated History of the United Trades and Labor Council, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- RS Pulled from drive - Erie County (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Marie Sachmowitz, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)